[Chopping wood]
What's wrong with that thing?
It's the signal.
I think.
Why don't you put that
thing down and look at nature
through your own
eyes for a change?
[Birds, nature sounds]
How's that dinner coming?
I'm wasting away over here.
Maybe if you helped,
you'd be eating already.
I'll help.
Okay. Thanks, sweetheart.
Come here.
Careful of the fire.
I know, mom.
[Fire crackling]
Uh, as long as you girls are
helping, I could use a hand
over here.
I am not chopping wood.
Like I would trust
you with an axe.
Whatever.
Seriously. Phone down.
The fire needs more wood.
Thanks, kiddo.
[Sudden boom]
[Ominous music]
You gotta help me.
Please. No, listen, listen.
He's gone crazy.
He's going crazy.
We have to get out of here.
All of us, we have to...
There's no time.
[Gunshot]
[Scream]
Get back! Please,
over here, here.
You okay?
Fuck!
Shit!
Put it down.
Put it down!
Okay, okay.
Move away from the axe.
[Music intensifying]
It's okay.
Is there a road nearby?
What?
A road!
That way.
Give me your keys.
Your keys!
Now!
Please.
It's okay.
Look,
I wasn't gonna hurt you.
Jesus. Did he touch you?
Did he touch you?
No. He just ran past.
He didn't hurt her.
I swear... he didn't.
It's okay.
[Music dies down]
Please.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
No!
[Jet engine sounds]
[Shaking sound]
[Clicking, static]
Man's bag is his life.
Don't mess with that.
I didn't touch your bag, man.
'Cause the last time some
asshole put a scorpion in my
bag to try and scare me.
That's an awful thing to do.
How childish.
Scorpions in each other's bags,
pissing in each other's beers.
When will it end?
Enjoy your beer.
[Turbulance]
Uh, almost got it on my shirt.
Could you even tell?
Bite me.
I guess three mill' doesn't
go far these days, hey?
I don't think that's
the plane, though.
Everything all right
up there, boss?
Approach. X-ray
X-ray November.
Say again.
[Dials clicking]
Approach. This is X-ray
X-ray November.
Come in.
[Plane rattles]
Is it turbulence?
No, I think it's electrical.
[Tense music]
You're not gonna
crash again, are you?
Approach X-ray X-ray November.
Approach. This is X-ray
X-ray November.
Do you read?
X-ray X-ray November.
Clear to land.
All right, ladies,
stow your seats
and leave it the
way you found it.
[Computer warning, "Burn out"]
["Engine failure"]
[Computer warning continues]
[Ominous music intensifying]
["Engine failure"]
[Warning alarms]
X-ray X-ray November.
Foxtrot X-ray X-ray November.
Radar contact.
Beware ILF operative
visual left traffic.
Should get lower
a little bit here.
[Computer warning
"Terrain, terrain, pull up"]
[Warning alarms continue]
[Tire screech]
[Military theme music]
[Military music continues]
[Jet engines wind down]
Thanks for the ride, Pete.
Stay out of trouble.
Always.
[Music fades]
Good to see you.
You too, Mac. How's Susan?
Sir?
Right.
We're on the
clock here, Dallas.
How's the flight?
Like this...
the closer we got.
Which is fine for you here,
but when you're 20,000 feet
in the air it's...
...gonna go over there.
Is that why we're here
instead of Wainwright?
It's part of it.
[People chatter]
Show them.
12 days ago, a UAP appeared out
of nowhere over our airspace,
traveling at over Mach five.
Approximately 30 seconds
after that
it suddenly lost
altitude and came down here.
Did you bring it down?
No. We scrambled C-130s
and fast movers
over the search
area and found the wreckage.
We recovered what we could
and set up a secure site in a
nearby abandoned mine here.
Why?
Let me guess, E.M. interference?
It wreaks havoc with
instruments and electrical
the closer you get.
We couldn't fly it out.
Luckily, we had an old logging
truck to ferry it
to the makeshift lab.
What is it?
We think it's a...
It's an experimental
Russian aircraft. Nothing more.
Who the hell are you?
I'm the guy paying you.
Spook central.
What's going on, Mac?
The mine shielded
the interference
until eight hours ago
when this happened.
[Computer analysing sounds]
That's not right.
The satellite's just
a really fancy camera high up.
Localized E.M.
wouldn't jank the
images like this.
Doesn't change the facts.
No signals in or out.
Can't even get a
bird to fly over it.
Over 70 personnel
working 'round the clock.
Haven't heard from a single
one of them since it went dark.
Whatever's happening
it's getting bigger.
Nearest town's Neandeg about
40 miles from the mine.
It's already getting affected.
This is above our pay grade.
What do you need us to do?
Our on site lead is
Doctor Moira Knight.
Basically an
astrophysics expert.
[Whistle]
If Hynek were alive, he'd
have her on speed dial.
Someone just got a hard on.
Oh, bro, you got no idea.
Go in,
get her personal hard drive
and engage
the kill switch.
It's a fail safe for the lab.
Triggers a series of explosions
that buries the mine and
whatever is inside it.
What about Doctor Knight?
SOP was to evac the moment
anything went sideways.
So that means anyone left
inside is considered hostile.
Got it?
We all have our orders, Dallas.
Copy that.
Any questions?
I suppose you're coming with us.
Do I look retarded?
You look like an asshole.
What was that?
I said, why us?
Taylor!
No, man.
We get sent in when
people need to be rescued.
Or need to disappear.
This is neither, save or grave.
Because everything we're
talking about is paid for by an
appropriations bill
that has nothing to
do with any of it.
None of us are even
here right now.
Plausible deniability.
So why not just use
a kinetic strike?
Bury it under the mountain?
The information stuck on that
hard drive represents a global
shift for whoever can
get their hands on it.
Uncle Sam wants it, and he's
going to be very generous when
he gets it.
So get to work.
The clock is ticking, Gentlemen.
Are you in or out?
[Energetic rock music]
[Water splashing]
[Road noise]
[Humvee rush by sound]
Blackhog Base
this is Blackhog One.
Traveling toward crossing
six... northing
on... break.
What road is this?
Damned if I know, just tell him
we're on highway three.
Past the offshoot
to Morris Lake.
Blackhog One, uh
...on the offshoot
past Morris Lake.
Copy, Blackhog One.
Continue to the next waypoint.
Copy?
[Rock music intensifies]
[Radio] "Blackhog One, copy?"
[Radio voice choppy]
Blackhog Base
this is Blackhog One
Say again all,
you're broken and unreadable.
Over.
They said this would happen.
Okay, I'm still not
clear on this.
If we're in such a hurry to get
there, why are we wasting so
much time driving?
Because if we took
a, uh,
plane in, we'd crash,
you dumb fuck!
Oh, I'm the dumb fuck.
You're half Native
and half Polish.
The last time you locked your
keys in your car, it took you
an hour to get your family out.
What do you call
an East Indian
not trying to sell
you something?
What?
A surprise!
Surprise...
I'm surprised you
remembered the punch line.
I'm also surprised you
could deliver that joke
in less than three hours.
Would you two shit heads
please keep it down?
I'm trying to read.
(Both)
Shut the fuck up!
All right.
There should be an old
logging road just up ahead.
Got it.
[Music continues]
So..
What's with you and
cats, anyway?
What can I say?
They're nature's
perfect killing machine.
They're silent,
agile and deadly.
All wrapped up in a mound of
fur that you just want to stuff
your face into.
Sounds like my ex.
[Laughter]
What can I say?
I love pussy in all its forms.
I like Taylor's Mom
in all its forms.
She's such a whore.
You fuck!
It's getting worse.
I think there's
a cream for that, Wolf.
Fuck. All right.
Head up this hill.
Skirt the river until
we reach the outcrop.
Copy that.
Blackhog Base
this is Blackhog One
transmitting
blind.
We're leaving
the hard pack at grid
four niner two
six four, out.
[Music resumes]
[Engine sputters
and dies]
[Starter motor cranking]
Looks like a nature
hike from here, boys.
See if you can reach base.
Should have been at least two
more miles until that happened.
On it, boss.
It's getting bigger.
That's what she said.
[Laughter]
Nothing but static, boss.
[Ominous music]
Taylor, you're on point.
Find me a way up
this fucking mountain.
You got it.
Let's go.
[Tense music]
[Haunting sound]
[Ominous music]
[Nature sounds]
[Slow tense music]
[Sudden overpowering sound]
What the hell is that?
I don't know.
It kind of made me feel dizzy.
More like a hangover.
Yeah, but...
Think of all the hair of
the dog you could buy
after we're done.
Hey, hey, we are not
doing this for money.
We're doing it for
a shit ton of money.
A shit ton of money.
Think of all the lives
you could change.
I'm going to invest
in green energy
and inner city youth.
Just fucking with you guys.
Hookers and guns?
Hookers and guns!
Dallas. We got a problem.
[Dark music]
I don't get it.
This doesn't add up.
These guys are Russian.
Maybe spec ops,
mercenaries, I don't know.
It's hard to say.
Okay, then why does it look
like they offed each other then?
Maybe one of them
drank all the vodka.
Sagan, you got anything?
[Radio static]
No. Just static still.
All right, we are flying solo,
and we are exposed.
It's about a mile to the mine.
And we are not alone.
Five meter spread.
Stay frosty.
[Military drums]
[Music intensifies]
[Gunshot]
[Woman screams]
[Gunshots]
What the hell?
Hold.
Help!
[Gunshot]
[Intense music building]
Hold...hold.
God damn it!
Push! Push!
[Multiple gunshots]
[Shouting in Russian]
[Music intensifies]
Wolf!
Rabbit! Go!
Sagan! Cover!
Hey, Tay-Tay, where do you
go after an explosion?
Dude, not right now.
[Explosion]
Everywhere.
Forty!
On it!
[Explosion]
Cleanup on aisle one.
Move!
Go. Clear!
Go.
[Gunshots]
Come on.
[Intense music]
[Gunshot]
Do you see him?
Up top.
I'll suppress.
Ready?
Rog.
[Multiple gunshots]
Go! I got this.
You sure?
I said go!
[Spooky music]
[Gunshot]
[Intense dark music]
[Sounds of struggling]
[Struggling, punching]
[Gunshot]
You've... killed... everyone.
That's the idea.
[Gunshot]
[Gunshot.]
A little help?!
I think that's all of them.
All you had to do was ask.
Wait.
[Gunshots]
What the hell, man?
Are you okay?
I'm good.
It's just a little
war paint, buddy.
You're right.
You good?
I'm good.
This guy's Russian, definitely.
AKs, same gear as before.
Yeah, but not all of them.
Something big is going on here.
Get up on that elevation.
See if you can reach anyone.
Rog.
What the fuck is happening?
This guy's wearing our colors.
I know this man.
He works for MacReady.
Then why the hell is
he shooting at us?
I don't know!
Nothing about this
makes any fucking sense!
Boss?
[Speaking in Russian]
He's Russian all right,
but if he's a grunt...
...then I'm the wrong
type of Indian.
You should be so lucky.
Hey.
You speak English?
Nothing but static.
You're Russian, right?
No, I'm Slovak.
Close enough.
Ask him what he's doing here.
[Speaking in Slovak]
[Speaking in Russian]
He says his name is Petrov
and uh, he's a pilot.
Wait, he was flying that bird?
No, no, he, uh...
He says he was chasing it.
What the hell does that mean?
I don't know.
He says everyone...
Everyone out there
just went crazy.
Everything else is
just gibberish, like...
I don't speak Russian.
What do you want to do, boss?
We keep going.
Bring him.
Gag him if you have to.
You sure you want to do that?
Agent man said no friendlies.
If he's got anything
to do with that plane,
he's been inside.
We keep him alive... for now.
But he doesn't...
He doesn't want to be touched.
Something...
something about the others.
Then tell him to put this
on and keep quiet.
Otherwise...
I'll cut his
fucking head off.
[Zip straps]
[Ominous music]
Boss, you think the Russians
did this?
Looks it.
[Sudden overpowering sound]
This shit is giving
me a headache.
It's coming from inside.
How can you tell?
At least they left
the door open.
Ok...
We do this by the numbers.
All right?
We go in, get what we need, and
get the fuck out of this place.
Yeah?
All right. On me.
[Spooky music]
[Metallic echoes in the deep]
[Spooky music rises]
[Sizzling and pipes clanging]
[Steam hissing]
[Scary music]
Looks like a fucking
war zone in here.
I guess we can rule
a lab accident
out of the question.
Did Wolf just make a joke?
Talk about a day of firsts.
The only people we've seen so
far are the few dozen outside...
Where are the rest?
[Deep music]
[Speaking in Russian]
Did I say stop?
He says he wants to go back.
I give two shits
what he wants.
Listen, pal, you have
one more strike left.
And that's all I'm
going to give you.
Do I make myself clear?
Good.
[Fingers snapping]
[Pipes rattle and echo]
[Spooky music intensifying]
[Music grows darker]
Hold up.
Which way to the main lab?
That door?
Or down this corridor?
[Speaking in Slovak]
[Speaking in Russian]
[Keyfob beep]
[Tense music rising]
[Shriek]
...the fuck is happening?
[Muffled]
Let me out!
I see you.
Let me out! Let me out!
Wolf.
[Intense, scary music]
[Wet thumps...]
What the hell?
[Thumping]
[Speaking in Russian]
I don't speak Russian.
Help me.
What the fuck?
Put it down.
Help me.
I'm not going to tell you again.
[Distorted]
Help me!
Drop her.
[Gunshots]
[Whirring and ringing]
[Door locks click open]
[Shriek]
[Hit, struggle]
[Neck snaps]
[Metal scraping]
[Door slam]
[Spooky music]
[Music grows tense]
[Metal scraping]
[Metallic thud]
[Sudden overpowering sound]
What is that?
[Water running]
Fuck!
What the actual fuck, man?
What's going on?
Help me.
Tell us what's happening.
It's not coming off!
Tay, I got the shot,
I'm gonna take it!
Hold up.
What won't come off?
Tay, I'm gonna take it!!
Stop!
Help me!
Gun!
[ROAR]
On our six!
Why won't you help me?
[Gunshots]
[Music builds]
[Metal thuds]
What the fuck?
This is fucked up.
[Thuds]
[Gunshots]
[Heavy thump]
Are you okay?
Took one hit to the plate.
[Distant shrieks]
We gotta go!
Shit! We gotta go!
[Heavy rhythmic music]
Oh shit!
You gotta be fucking
kidding me!
Come on! Come on!
[Gunshots]
Move it!
Go!
Sagan! Let's go!
Move it! Move it!
[Wet shrieks and groans]
Stairs!
Wolf!
Card!
Shit... breach.
[Unlock click]
Go... go go go.
We're not going
back out that way.
Fucking psychos.
Whatever that was,
that wasn't psychosis.
Did you see their faces?
Their necks?
The veins?
It's more like an infection.
By what?
I don't know, but this isn't
just about plane
parts anymore.
Wolf? You good?
Wolf?
[Cutting]
Yeah. Okay.
Okay. So where are we now?
Twelve days, my ass.
This place has been
here for years.
What are the chances a
Russian bird
crashes right beside
a black site?
Yeah. Something
stinks, all right.
Main lab's
got to be close.
Taylor, find me a back door.
You got it.
Rest of you, keep an eye out.
Maybe we can find out what
the hell is going on in here.
Let's go.
[Tense music]
[Glass breaking]
Shit.
Clear.
[Lockpick sounds]
[Unlock click]
[Buzzing]
[Sizzle]
[Tense music building]
Clear!
Okay, see what you
can find out.
So you know what
she did next, man?
My ex.
She bought a fucking dog.
Dogs are awesome.
Not when you have a cat. Mittens
couldn't sleep for a week.
Don't tell me you slept
on the couch with the cat.
What was I supposed to do?
I worry about you.
Man...
I can't make heads or tails
of half of this stuff.
Don't you have a
master's degree?
Like I said, whatever
we stumbled on here,
it's huge.
What do you mean?
This? This is a
Metallurgic test report.
This is a metal
that doesn't exist.
And this autopsy report?
I'll be damned if I can
figure out what they cut open.
What are you saying?
I'm saying I don't think a
Russian plane crashed
in those woods.
Okay, but what about this
guy and his buddies outside?
Beats me.
I think they stumbled onto
something they shouldn't have.
A lot of that
going around today.
Why not?
[Military theme music]
What are we drinking to?
A day of firsts.
[Speaking in Russian]
Here's to colors
that never run.
[Glasses clinking]
Hey!
I think I found our way out.
There's an old emergency exit.
It's blocked up,
but I cleared it.
Finally, some good news.
That's not all.
Show us.
Come on.
[Overwhelming sound]
My head feels like it's gonna
split in two when that happens.
I think we're getting
closer to the source.
You're right on top of... it.
What took you so long?
Jesus. We gotta get her out.
You move this off me
and I'll bleed to death.
Wait! Don't come any closer.
You can't touch me.
That's what it wants.
What are you talking about?
It's bioelectric.
Like nanites.
Only not.
We thought we took precautions.
[Distorted scream]
That shit's killing her.
Killing, right.
Right, right.
Killing... A high enough
current might do it.
Of course it'll kill
the host too.
Host?
Are you saying you're
infected with something?
Is that what's happening
with everybody here?
Not everybody.
They tried to contain...
Tried.
[Distorted scream]
They tricked us...
They knew we would
take the bait.
It overwrites nervous
system... brain stem.
You don't even notice.
that's the worst part.
Doctor.
Where are your files?
Jesus, man, really?
Files, files.
Files. Right, um,
God, it's so hard
to think.
It needs a living host.
If you kill the host,
the virus dies too.
Doctor...
your files?
A man of orders.
I can respect that.
And the kill switch?
I would have but...
circumstances.
The virus,
did it start with the crash?
Autopsy.
Is it airborne?
Did you...?
Did you touch anyone?
Any of you?
We did meet some resistance
coming in.
Resist...?
No, no, no, they they
came to get their man.
But he wasn't...
not anymore.
Not anymore.
[Gunshots]
Too much talking.
The fuck are you doing?
[Gunshots]
No!
[Speaking in Russian]
Mother fu...
Why?
Take it.
Find out.
What the fuck's
that supposed to mean?
[Cough] He's infected.
They both are.
Boss?
The drive.
Why do you want it?
He's right.
There are bigger
things in play here.
Don't let him touch you.
Give me the drive
and I walk away.
It'll all be over soon anyway.
You know I can't do that.
I know.
Go!
[Flashbang exploding]
[High pitch ringing]
Go go go go go!
Go!
Aw, fuck!
Go go.
Go go go.
[Gunshots]
[Gunshot and hit]
You good?
Plate took it!
What do we do?
The woods, woods...
We get... to the Humvee.
We split up.
Go, go!
Nature's...
perfect killer.
[Heavy drums]
What the fuck, man?
It's amazing what a
little love tap can do.
Jesus Christ, that works fast.
You have no idea.
It's still me.
With just a little...
upgrade.
Yeah? Like
those people back there?
Give me your hand.
We can be on the same side.
Yeah? What side is that?
All right.
Don't say I've never
done anything for you.
[Speaking in Russian]
[Intense music]
[Explosions]
[Screeching]
[Gunshots]
Stand the fuck down, man!
[Struggles and punching]
[Intense music, drums]
Please, stop it!
[Roar]
[Knife unsheathing, stab]
Too late.
Just... give... in.
[Gunshots]
No!
Fuck...
[Music - Lament]
[Raven's cry]
Can't even touch him, man.
I can't even take
him home with us.
We have to go.
What am I supposed to do?
Where's your heart?
Huh?
Where's your fucking heart?!
You know why the
Natives hate snow?
Because it's white, and it's
all over their fucking land!
I just killed my brother.
And you did too.
All we have is each other now.
Do we?
Has to be skin to skin.
Who says?
He didn't turn
till he got his nose broke.
How do you know that?
If you got a better
theory, man, I'm waiting.
But Knight said,
if the host dies,
the virus dies.
And we don't even
know how long that is.
Sagan has all the
long range equipment.
If we don't make it back,
they're going to start digging
in that dirt looking for answers
and it'll spread like wildfire.
The humvee.
It has a radio
that should work.
All right.
But we agree right now,
no human contact
until we get cleared.
And if one of us tries...
He eats a bullet.
It's not about
the money anymore.
Not anymore.
[Military drums]
[Nature sounds]
All right.
I figure if we--
Fuck.
What?
[Quiet, ominous music]
You know,
they never tell you
when you're young...
One day you're
going to get tired,
and you'll never stop
being tired.
Don't make me do this, man.
I'd do it myself,
but, um...
You can't trust me with that.
There has to be another way.
Maybe I can tie you
up or something.
We can't take that chance.
Please.
It's been an honor, boss.
[Click]
Wait.
I don't...
I don't feel different.
Shouldn't I feel... something?
How the hell am I
supposed to know?
I think... [Sniff]
I think we should wait.
[Rhythmic music]
[Gunshots]
[Gunshot, yell]
[Splash]
Shit.
[Low, tense music]
[Wood chop]
[Chop]
What's wrong with that thing?
It's the signal... I think.
Why don't you put that
thing down and look at nature
through your own
eyes for a change?
How's that dinner coming?
I'm wasting away over here.
Maybe if you helped,
you'd be eating by now.
I'll help.
Careful with the fire.
I know, Mom. [Chop]
Uh, as long as you girls
are helping,
I could use a
hand over here.
I... am not chopping wood.
Like I... would trust
you with an axe.
Whatever.
Seriously, phone down,
the fire needs more wood.
[Chop]
Thanks, kiddo.
[Music boom]
Please, you gotta help me.
You don't understand.
He's gone crazy.
We have to get out of here.
Oh, no.
We have to get...
Please. Please help me!
[Gunshot]
Ah!
[Scream]
Shit!
No!
- Put it down!
Put it down!
Ok.
Move away.
Is there a road nearby?
What?
A road!
That way.
Give me your keys.
What?!
Give me your keys! Now!
Ok.
Please.
It's okay.
Look.
I wasn't going to do anything.
Jesus! Did he touch you?
No. He just ran past us all.
He didn't hurt her, I swear.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
No! [Gunshots]
Oh, God.
[Door latch]
[Door slamming]
Ahhhh!
This...
This isn't fun anymore.
I don't know...[Coughing]
I'm starting to enjoy it.
[Hard hits]
Come on.
Stay with me.
Hey hey hey.
Don't pass out, don't pass out.
Look at you.
Look at you!
All that anger and doubt.
See those innocent
people you just murdered?
Huh? You didn't really know,
did you? [Chuckle]
Let me tell you a secret.
It doesn't even matter.
Oh, speaking of which.
Remember this?
[Gunshot]
It happens faster
than you think.
You're not gonna get
far on that leg, though.
You take five.
And I'll meet you in town.
All right?
You can do it.
And this...
is just in case anybody
tries to stop you.
[Reloading]
[Intense music, whoosh,
alien sounds]
Ahhh!
[Explosions]
[Screams]
[Heartbeat]
[Moaning]
[Grunting]
Current...
Current!
[Ominous music]
[Sizzle, groan]
[Boom, sizzle]
[Distant boom]
Finally...
[Military drums rising]
[Window rolling down]
What in the Sam Hill
are you doing, man?
Trying to get run oh, oh...
What's your name?
Your name!
Marv, Marvin.
Okay, Marv, Marvin.
I'm gonna give you a choice.
You drive me to town,
or I can shoot you dead.
Uh...
Hop in?
Good call.
[Gasping]
Thank God.
[Grunting, coughing]
Ahhh!
Come on.
[Starter clicking]
Come on!
Damn it!
[Engine starting]
Yes! Yes!
[Energetic music]
Good day at the lake, Marv?
You're not gonna take
my catch, are you?
Just keep your
hands on ten and two
and let me know if there's
anyone behind us.
[Peaceful music]
Don't.
I like that song.
[Peaceful music]
[Low military drums]
I said...
ten and two, Marv.
You told me to wake
you if I saw somebody.
[Ominous tone]
You got a cell phone, Marv?
Local calls only, right?
[Dialing... ringing]
Blackhog One to Blackhog Base.
Zero One Bravo...
Tango Three Zulu.
This is Taylor to
Blackhog Base.
You copy?
State your designation.
Zer...One.. Bravo.. tang...
Lu.
God damn it!
Give me Hiller.
It's no use, Ma'am.
Blackhog Base to Blackhog One.
What is your status?
Thank God.
Hiller, this is Taylor.
I'm on highway three,
approx... 15 mile...
Neandeg.... I'm in pursuit
of a red pickup truck.
Do you copy?
Copy, Blackhog One.
My team is dead.
Dallas is in the red...
He's infected with a pathogen
that spreads through
human contact.
Say again,
Blackhog One?
They knew.
They knew when it crashed
that you'd go digging around...
...tear it apart,
including the pilot.
It was a trap!
We were the Indians,
and they gave us diseased
fucking blankets.
He's infected.
If he makes it to
town, it's game over.
You hear me?
Game over!
You copy that?!
Hiller?
Hiller?!
Shit!
[Engine revving]
[Intense music rising]
[Loud thud, tire screech]
Ah, jeez.
[Gunshots]
Son of a bitch.
[Tire screech]
Why won't you quit?
[Gunshots]
Speed up.
Drive faster! Lose him!
It's not a race car.
Then make it one!
[Bullet hit, steam hiss]
No, no,
Fuck. No!
[Engine sputtering]
[Chuckles] It's over.
Ah...
[Pats shoulder]
Nice going, Marv.
Didn't know
you had it in you.
No matter what happens,
don't stop.
Oh, shit.
Oh! Thank God.
Oh, oh, Thank God!
Stop or we will fire!
I said, don't stop.
They're gonna kill us!
What do you think I'm gonna do?
[Truck horn]
[Engine revving]
[Gunshot]
[Glass breaking, hit]
Look what you did.
Well, shit.
Get out of your vehicle.
You won't get another warning.
[Reloading]
Keep those hands up.
Walk slowly towards us.
That's good right there.
Thank God you got my messages.
We got both your messages.
What?
We found Knight alive.
He turned on us.
She's dead.
Along with the rest of my team.
Motherfucker!
Don't you move!
He destroyed her hard drive and
slaughtered an entire family
just so he could catch up to me.
Is that true?
That's their van.
You'll find them at a
campground 25 miles back.
Shot to death.
You can't believe a
thing that he says.
Did you kill innocent people?
I had to.
Like I said, I don't know if
the Russians got to him or
someone else.
But you can't trust this man.
Colonel MacReady, may I?
Nice and easy.
Those are her notes.
She died for this!
Everybody did!
I know how to stop this.
This is bullshit, Mac.
I can't believe you'd take the
word of a traitor over a friend.
Look at him.
He's barely holding it together!
That's what this shit does!
It gets in your
head, it uses you,
and then it makes you go crazy.
That's what happened at the lab.
They take me in, cuff
me, interrogate me.
I'll tell you
everything I know.
Hmm?
Hiller, arrest these men.
No!
[Fight]
[Rhythmic percussion]
[Distorted]
Ahhh!
Hiller! Arrest them!
Colonel.
Delay that order.
You're not in charge here.
Is that so?
Sorry, Colonel.
We all have our orders.
Let's see how this plays out.
[Haunting voice]
You will die...
See? take a look,
he's infected!
It spreads through
human contact!
Ahh!!
[Stab]
Not on your best day.
[Overpowering sound]
Can you feel it?
Huh?
You think this is the only
place they staged this?
Oh, you're in for a shock.
This whole world
is in for a shock!
[Gunshot]
Kill the host.
Kill the virus.
You have to kill us both!
[UFO powering up from above]
Yahhh!!!
[Soldiers screaming]
Make it stop! Make it stop!
It's okay, Taylor.
It's okay.
I'm not tired anymore.
[Chuckle]
[Deep, ominous pulses]
[UFO moving]
[UFO races away]
[Music, Military theme]
[Music, Rock theme]